(AMBIENCE)
(ENGINES REVVING)
♪ ♪ ♪
♪ PULLIN' OUT THE COUPE AT THE
LOT ♪
♪ TOLD 'EM "----
12, ---- SWAT" ♪
♪ BUSTIN' ALL THE BALES OUT THE
BOX ♪
♪ I JUST HIT A
LICK WITH THE BOX ♪
♪ HAD TO PUT THE ----- IN A BOX,
MM ♪
♪ POUR UP THE WHOLE DAMN SEAL,
I'MA GET LAZY ♪
♪ I GOT THE MOJO-DEALS, WE BEEN
TRAPPIN' LIKE THE '80'S ♪
♪ SHE SUCKED A ----- SOUL, GOT
THE CASH APP ♪
♪ TOLD 'EM WIPE A ----- NOSE,
SAY SLATT, SLATT ♪
♪ I WON'T NEVER SELL MY SOUL,
AND I CAN BACK THAT ♪
♪ AND I REALLY WANNA KNOW, WHERE
YOU AT, AT? ♪
♪ I WAS OUT BACK, WHERE THE
STASH AT ♪
♪ CRUISE THE CITY IN A
BULLETPROOF CADILLAC (SKRRT) ♪
♪ 'CAUSE I KNOW THESE ━━━ AFTER
WHERE THE BAG AT ♪
♪ GOTTA MOVE SMARTER, GOTTA MOVE
HARDER ♪
♪ ━━━ TRYNA GET
ME FOR MY WATER ♪
♪ I LAY HIS --- DOWN ON MY SON
OR MY DAUGHTER ♪
♪ I HAD THE ------ WITH ME,
DWAYNE CARTER ♪
♪ 'LOTTA ------ OUT HERE
PLAYIN', AIN'T BALLIN' ♪
♪ I DONE PUT MY WHOLE ARM IN THE
RIM, VINCE CARTER ♪
♪ AND I KNOW PROBABLY GET A ━
FOR THE QUARTER ♪
♪ SHAWTY BARELY SEEN IN DOUBLE
C'S I BOUGHT HER ♪
♪ GOT A ----- THAT'S LOOKING
LIKE AALIYAH, SHE A MODEL ♪
♪ I GOT THE PINK SLIP, ALL MY
WHIPS IS KEY-LESS ♪
♪ COMPTON, I'M ABOUT TO GET THE
KEY TO THE CITY ♪
♪ PATEK LIKE THE
SEA, FORGET IT ♪
♪ PULLIN' OUT THE COUPE AT THE
LOT ♪
♪ TOLD 'EM "----
12, ---- SWAT" ♪
♪ BUSTIN' ALL THE BALES OUT THE
BOX ♪
♪ I JUST HIT A
LICK WITH THE BOX ♪
♪ HAD TO PUT THE ----- IN A BOX,
MM ♪
♪ POUR UP THE WHOLE DAMN SEAL,
I'MA GET LAZY ♪
♪ I GOT THE MOJO-DEALS, WE BEEN
TRAPPIN' LIKE THE '80'S ♪
♪ SHE SUCKED A ----- SOUL, GOT
THE CASH APP ♪
♪ TOLD 'EM WIPE A ----- NOSE,
SAY SLATT, SLATT ♪
♪ I WON'T NEVER SELL MY SOUL,
AND I CAN BACK THAT ♪
♪ AND I REALLY WANNA KNOW, WHERE
YOU AT, AT? ♪
♪ HA-HA-HA, I BEEN
MOVIN' 'EM OUT ♪
♪ IF STEELO WITH ME, THEN HE GOT
THE BLUES IN THE POUCH ♪
♪ TOOK HER TO THE FOREST, PUT
THE ━━ ━ ━ ━━ ♪
♪ ━━ DON'T WEAR NO SHOES IN MY
HOUSE ♪
♪ THE PRIVATE I'M FLYIN' IN, I
NEVER WANNA FLY AGAIN ♪
♪ I TAKE MY CHANCES IN TRAFFIC ♪
♪ SHE ━━━ ━ ━━ NO
HANDS WITH IT ♪
♪ I JUST MADE THE ROLLIE PLAIN
LIKE A LANDING-STRIP ♪
♪ I'M A 2020
PRESIDENT CANDIDATE ♪
♪ I DONE PUT A HUNNID BANDS ON
ZIMMERMAN ---- ♪
♪ I BEEN MOVIN' REAL GANGSTA, SO
THAT'S WHY SHE PICK A ━━- ♪
♪ SHAWTY CALL ME CRISCO, 'CAUSE
I POP MY ---- ♪
♪ GOT IT OUT THE MUD, THERE'S
NOTHIN' YOU CAN TELL ME, YEAH ♪
♪ WHEN I HAD THE ━━━, I WAS
STREET-WEALTHY, YEAH ♪
♪ PULLIN' OUT THE COUPE AT THE
LOT ♪
♪ TOLD 'EM "----
12, ---- SWAT" ♪
♪ BUSTIN' ALL THE BALES OUT THE
BOX ♪
♪ I JUST HIT A
LICK WITH THE BOX ♪
♪ HAD TO PUT THE ----- IN A BOX,
MM ♪
♪ POUR UP THE WHOLE DAMN SEAL,
I'MA GET LAZY ♪
♪ I GOT THE MOJO-DEALS, WE BEEN
TRAPPIN' LIKE THE '80'S ♪
♪ SHE SUCKED A ----- SOUL, GOT
THE CASH APP ♪
♪ TOLD 'EM WIPE A ----- NOSE,
SAY SLATT, SLATT ♪
♪ I WON'T NEVER SELL MY SOUL,
AND I CAN BACK THAT ♪
♪ AND I REALLY WANNA KNOW, WHERE
YOU AT, AT? ♪
♪ ♪ ♪
(MUSIC ENDS)